THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
拉瓦 听着
Rava. Hey.
我爸...
Uh, my dad's...
我爸进医院了
My dad's in the hospital.
对 他... 我也不清楚
Yeah, he had, I don't know,
我也不知道什么病
I don't know what.
但是...
But, uh...
我不知道他还会不会好起来
yeah, I don't know if he's gonna be OK.
这... 对
It's... Yeah.
就... 我也不知道 我跟杰西在一起
So... I don't know. I'm here with Jess.
我们正在往那儿赶
We're just trying to get there...
搞什么...
What the...?
我们可以绕过这片堵车吗 哥们
Can we just find a way around the traffic, man?
你... 就想想办法吧 拜托
Just... Just... Just figure it out. Please!
重症监护室在哪
Where's the ICU?
... 血压...
... blood pressure...
... 化验...
... tests...
情况怎样了 有人能...
What's the situation? Can somebody...
打扰
Excuse me.
他们在抢救呢
They're working on him.
这里是医院的什么部分
What is this part of the hospital?
这是最好的科室吗
I mean, is this the best section?
打扰一下 医生
Excuse me? Doctor,
这是医院里最好的地方吗
is this the best part of the hospital?
抱歉 我们只想知道
Sorry. You know, we just-- we need to know.
重症监护室就是重症监护室 这里对他来说最好
The ICU is the ICU. This is the best place for him.
你爸也会来这里治疗吗
Is this where you would take your father?
抱歉 请给医疗小组一点空间 好吗
I'm sorry. Can the team have some space? Please?
这样吧 你还是多担心担心用药
Hey, here's an idea. Why don't you worry about the medicine,
而不是他娘的风水
not the fucking feng shui?
让医生好好抢救
Let's let the gentleman do his job.
谢谢
Thank you.
-为了爸安静点  -谢谢
- Let's do this for Dad. - Thank you.
抱歉
Sorry.
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 我的后面是猪精
翻译: 李木木
翻译: 莉莉安
翻译: Graaace
翻译: QueenBear
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 豆
时间轴: 雅子
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第２集
"浑沌企业的滑稽秀"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
他们知道我们是谁吗
Do they know who we are?
-我不知道  -他们是在搪塞我们吗
- I don't know. - Are they sandbagging us?
-他们知道他是谁吗  -我不知道
- Do they know who he is? - I don't know.
-我们要给妈打电话吗  -什么
- Shall we call Mom? - What?
不行 有那么多人的电话你不打
No. There's like a million people to call.
她总归会把注意引回自己身上
She's probably just make it about herself, anyway.
拜托 你妈是个疯子 又不是怪物
Come on. Your mom's a maniac, she's not a monster.
伙计们 请你们在那里等待
Folks, we need you to wait through there, please.
你好 打扰了
Hi. I'm sorry.
我们听说了杂七杂八的消息
We're getting mixed messages here.
完全搞不清到底什么情况
We have no clue what's going on.
出结果以后
We will be with you
我们会马上通知你们
as soon as we have an assessment.
好吧 这样还不够
OK, well, that's not good enough.
我们要知道到底什么情况 马上
We need to know what's happening. Now.
几大洲的社会经济状况
The socio-economic health of multiple continents
都取决于他的健康
is dependent on his well-being.
几大洲的社会经济状况
The socio-economic health of multiple continents?
肯德尔 各位
Kendall. Everyone.
我们可以去一个地方等
We have an area we can go to.
他们会随时通知我们
They'll keep us posted.
听着 跟我说一遍到底发生了什么
So, look, take me through what happened exactly.
我也不清楚
Uh, I don't know, exactly.
很奇怪 发生得很突然
It was weird. Um, it happened fast,
-我们就坐在那里...  -聊着天
- we were just sitting there... - We were just talking.
我们在聊天 小西开始
We were talking, Shiv kind of started
-跟爸爸硬杠  -我才没有硬杠
- hard-balling Dad a little bit. - I wasn't hard-balling him.
闲聊才不会引起脑出血 傻逼
A brain hemorrhage doesn't come from some chit-chat, asshole.
确定是脑出血吗 医生是这么说的
So it's definitely a brain hemorrhage? Is that what they said?
总有人说了 对吧
Somebody said that, right?
-有人说是脑出血了吗  -还是中风 我...
- Somebody said hemorrhage? - Or stroke? I...
-救护车...  -中风就是脑出血
- The ambulance... - A stroke is a hemorrhage.
-是吗  -是的
- It is? - Yes.
是别人说了"脑出血"
Did someone say "Hemorrhage,"
还是我们自己人瞎说的
or is it just us who said it?
可能是动脉瘤
It could be an aneurism.
为什么不搞清楚点
Why aren't we chasing this?
交给我吧
I'll chase.
那啥 有人...
Hey, uh, is there any...
冷冻法: 将人体冰冻起来 再在未来某个时候苏醒
爸有跟你们说起过冷冻法吗
Did Dad ever talk to any of you guys about cryogenics?
你已经疯了
You're insane.
听着 我不想跟这里的
Look, I don't want to be given the runaround
纽约州立大学医学院高材生兜圈子
by Doctor-fucking-SUNY Purchase Medical School here.
我们要去问谁是这家医院最好的医生
We need to know who the top players are, OK?
最顶尖的医生是哪个
Who's the top dog in this hospital?
你跟爸的神经科医师谈过没有
Have you talked to Dad's neurologist?
肯德尔 别像医院的国王一样指手画脚
Kendall, stop acting like the king of the hospital.
我们都尽力了 你他妈一边凉快去吧
We're all trying to do our best, so just fuck off.
我在问了 好吗
I'm on it. OK?
据这上面说 很像中风
According to this, it sounds like a stroke,
但也有可能是急性硬脑膜下血肿
but it could be an acute subdural hematoma.
"真棒" 快上手术台吧 谷歌医生
Great. Get in there and operate, Doctor Google.
他跟我说过一次冷冻法
He once talked to me about cryogenics.
怎么了 这不是很正常吗
What? Wouldn't that just be typical?
其他亿万富翁都换了新的器官到处溜达
All the other billionaires are strolling around in new bodies,
除了老爸 因为我们觉得
but not Dad, because we were
讨论这事太尴尬了
too embarrassed to actually discuss it.
不是他跟你谈过冷冻法
He didn't talk to you about cryogenics.
而你跟他提起过
You talked to him about cryogenics
因为你对这个念念不忘
because you're obsessed with cryogenics.
-我没有 肯德尔  -他没有告诉过你
- I'm not really, Kendall. - And what he didn't tell you,
而我正要告诉你的是
and what I'm telling you now,
你就是个白痴
is that you are an idiot.
半斤八两 肯尼
Sticks and stones, Kenny.
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
还在他生日当天 太倒霉了
And on his birthday, too? It's so shitty.
那现在怎么办
So what's happening now?
你要陪在医院吗
Are you staying at the hospital?
大概吧
I guess.
我应该找到工作了
I mean, I think I've got a job,
但我也不知道
but I don't know.
洛根说我拿下了
Logan said I did,
但只有玛西娅听到了
but Marcia was the only one to hear it,
所以... 然后他就不幸地
so... and then he tragically,
算了 随便吧
you know, like, whatever.
哪种工作 是份好工作吗
Well, what sort of job? Is it a good job?
说不好
I don't know. Like,
什么都可能
could be anything.
我身上只剩120块了
And I have, like, 20 bucks left.
这个世界真是一团糟
The world is so fucked up.
我不会再给你寄钱了 格雷格
I am not sending you any more money, Greg.
自己想办法
Step up.
我没想问你要钱...
I'm not asking you to send me...
听着
Look,
一定要拿到那份工作
just make sure about the job.
-行吗  -好的 知道了
- All right?  - Yeah, I know.
你有现金吗
Hey, do you have cash?
等一下...
Yeah. Uh...
没了 我只有这点了
no, just my last twenty.
够了 谢谢
That's fine. Thanks.
我刚刚被小西打劫了
I just got mugged by Shiv.
出生于正值二战爆发前夕
Born in humble circumstances in Dundee, Scotland,
苏格兰邓迪市内谦逊的文化环境中
shortly before the outbreak of the Second World War,
洛根·罗伊出生自贫穷
Logan Roy grew up in poverty,
离世时却成为美国
but died one of the richest
最具权势和家财的人之一
and most powerful men in America.
他的单亲母亲决定...
His widowed mother took the decision...
这是泛美网络科技公司拟的讣告
It's an ATN obituary.
他们想要咱们的授权 以防万一
They want us to OK it in case they have to run it.
觉得怎么样
Is it nice?
毕竟他自己新闻部做出来的
I mean, it's made by his own news division.
没骂他是个混球
Doesn't say he was a prick.
你要看吗
You want to watch it?
不用
No.
我很想跟你见面
I would really love to see you.
不会 没什么不合适的 再合适不过了
Yes, it's appropriate. It could hardly be more appropriate.
行吗
Ok?
好的 好 好 很好
Yeah, OK. OK, good.
-杰西  -怎么了
- Hey, Jess? - Mm-hmm?
这里没有任何关于我母亲
There's nothing in here about our mom.
还有康纳的内容 得把他们加进去
Or Connor's. They need to be included.
好的
Yeah.
PJ说"梅奥诊所"的阿齐兹·卡恩是最顶尖的专家
PJ says Aziz Kahn at Mayo Clinic is the best there is.
萨拉说是纽约大学的安·威依曼
Sarah says Ann Wieman at NYU.
安·威依曼 那不是... 她不是我的人
Ann Wieman? Is that... That's not who I have.
但她的名字在我手上
Well, it's the name I have.
让萨拉给她打个电话
Can you tell Sarah to give her a call?
-好的  -给你 小罗
- Sure. - Hey, Rome.
-有全糖的吗  -没有 我只买了...
- Do you have regular?  - No, I've got...
我身无分文了 刚有找零吗
Now I'm strapped. Was there any change at all?
-大家  -怎么了
- Hey, you guys. - What?
能把找零给我吗
Could I have the change?
这是啥 已经有人开始送这破玩意了吗
What is this? Already? People are sending shit already?
沃尔特公司的劳伦斯·易送的
It's from Lawrence Yee at Vaulter.
打电话跟他讲谢谢他八辈祖宗
Call him and tell him that is not fucking appreciated.
收到
Mm-hmm.
-肯德尔 我很遗憾  -谢谢 格丽
- Kendall, I'm so sorry. - Thank you, Gerri.
耽误你五分钟
Can you give me five?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
这边 请
Over here, OK?
很显然提名委员会和董事会
Obviously the nominating committee, the board,
就洛根的现况制定了计划
has a plan in the event of Logan's incapacitation.
不好意思 现在非得讲这些吗
Sorry, do I need to hear this right now?
非讲不可
You do.
就目前的情况 如果我们
In the event that we, uh,
想要基于他的意识情况
continue on our trajectory
保持原计划继续进行
of his current consciousness,
就得宣布一个计划
we're gonna need to announce a plan
最迟6点30左右 得在开市前
by around 6:30, before the markets open,
不能被爱吃鬼巧达们钻了空子[美国动画人物]
in order to avoid a lot of funky chowder.
你刚刚说了爱吃鬼巧达
Did you say funky chowder?
我们在那边布置好了
We've set up down here.
你们布置什么了
What have you set up?
你需要一个地方
You're gonna want a place to just be,
冷静冷静 懂吧
and chill, you know?
我们和院方负责人谈过了
We talked to some of the trustees of the hospital,
现在大家都知道我们是谁
so everybody knows who's who.
没错 这还不算是作战室 但...
Yeah. It's not a war room yet, but, um...
一旦需要 就能派上用场
But if we need one, it's available.
天呐
Jesus.
穿过那边是卫生间...
Uh, so there's a bathroom through there...
-你好 卡洛丽娜...  -好
- Hi, Karolina...  - Hi.
辛苦了 大家
Thank you, guys.
提名委员会的戴维和阿沙在电话线上
So I have Dewi and Asha from the nominating committee on the line.
肯德尔来了 我把扬声器打开了
Kendall's here, and you're on speaker, guys.
我们大家得知消息都深表遗憾
So sorry to hear about the news.
深表遗憾
Likewise.
如你所知 我们制定的长期计划以应对洛根的...
As you know, our standing plan in the event of Logan's...
缺席 将暂停他的总裁和董事长职务
absence, is to separate his CEO and Chairman roles.
由你来做代理总裁
You'll become acting CEO,
弗兰克继续做首席运营官
Frank stays on as COO.
我们得立马行动起来 稳定股价
We'll need to act fast. Stabilize the stock price.
戴维 戴维
Dewi? Dewi?
不好意思...
I'm sorry...
我现在只关心我爸的安危 懂吗
my dad is my focus right now, OK?
当然 但假如今天早些时候
Of course, it's just that there's a problem
发生在你俩身上的事传出去
in terms of the optics if what happened earlier today
我们就麻烦了
between you two gets out.
不好意思 我不懂你在说什么
I'm sorry, I don't know what you're talking about.
"当然了"...
Sure. Well...
然后弗兰克那里又出了问题
And then there's the problem with Frank.
-什么问题  -洛根炒了他
- As in?  - Logan fired him
给罗曼升了职
and promoted Roman.
罗曼
Roman?
我的天
Jesus.
听着 很抱歉 我...
Look, I'm sorry, I...
各位 我现在不能参与进来
I can't get into this right now, guys.
不 不用抱歉
No, of course.
你现在状态不佳[进退两难]
You are in no fit state.
但我是这么想的
But here's my take, OK?
我爸今天病了 对吧
My dad got sick today, right?
我不知道 我是说 没人知道
I don't know, I mean, nobody knows
他从什么时候起变得举止古怪
when he started acting out of character,
但是 他好像从早上看起来就不大好
but, like, he didn't seem great from the morning on,
今天也没有签订任何职位变动的合同
and there's no paper on any of the moves made today.
-对吗 格丽  -这...
- Right, Gerri? - Uh...
没签过什么重要的
nothing meaningful.
他就那么一说
Yeah, it was words.
说出来的话呢
Words are just, what?
不算数的
Nothing.
只是复杂的气流变换
Complicated air flow.
所以 我觉得 今天什么事都没发生
So, I mean, if I was saying what actually happened today,
什么都没有
it would be nothing.
好吧 那的确
Well, that certainly
从我们的角度出发是有利的
makes things simpler from our point of view.
你觉得家族会支持你吗
Do you think you can get the family behind it?
会
Yes.
弗兰克呢
And Frank?
也会的
Sure.
哥 不能在这聊吗
Dude, can't we just talk here?
你知道康纳把威拉请过来了吗
You know Connor's invited Willa down?
啥玩意 来了吗
What?! Here?!
他俩跟咱们有啥关系
What's the deal with their deal?
和我不一样 他完全没有界限感
Unlike me, he has no sense of boundaries.
这什么鬼
What the fuck?
臭了点 但起码没人 我觉得
It's stale, but it's empty, I think.
-有人吗  -你要上台演一出吗
- Hello? - You wanna do a play?
不 我 只是想...
No, I, um, just wanted to...
我一直在想现在这种情况可能
I've been thinking that maybe this might be
让玛西娅很煎熬
really tough on Marcia.
是吗 你真这么想
Yeah, you're thinkin' that?
咋了 你觉得她想把自己分到的遗产全变成金子或石油吗
What, will she put all her inheritance into gold or oil?
不 我只是... 不是 我...
No, I just... No, I...
听着 我知道只有特定的事情发生后
Look, I know that, like, the trust only comes into play
才会上演信托戏码...
if certain things happen...
就像现在 他死了 或脑死亡啥的
Yeah, he's dead, or brain dead.
对 但我在想...
Yeah, but I was thinkin', like...
如果让老爸醒过来
wouldn't it be nice for Dad to wake up
我们所有人如他所愿把字签了
and for all of us to have signed,
不是更好吗
like he wanted?
也就是说 示好
You know, like a nice gesture?
万一他醒不过来呢
And if he doesn't wake up,
我们岂不是白纸黑字让权给玛西娅
we've basically signed over to Marcia
让她可以光明正大地找个后爹
the power to choose the new Dad.
好吧... 所以 你的声明是
So... OK. So, for the record,
你打算拒不同意信托变更
you are declining to sign on the change of trust?
-我的声明  -是啊
- For the record? - Yeah.
麦卡锡主义: 恶意诽谤、肆意迫害 疑似共产党和民主进步人士
这是什么鬼 麦卡锡主义吗
What the fuck is this, McCarthyism?
我不是在拒绝 我只是...
I'm not declining, I'm just not...
不"倾向" 操...
I'm not "Clining." What the f...
好的 没关系 你懂的
OK. No. OK, just, you know,
只是这种情况这么做有点卑鄙而已
that just seems very shitty under the circumstances.
什么情况
What circumstances?
你要承认是你害她丈夫脑溢血的
Well, you did make her husband's brain explode.
去你妈的
Fuck you, man!
等等...
Wait...
-别打了  -你个混蛋
- Stop it! - You shit!
你他妈疯了吗
What, are you fuckin' insane?
住手 住手
No! No!
他...
He...
不该是这样的
He doesn't deserve this.
太不公平了
It's just so unfair.
他是个... 好人
He's a great... man.
他让我参加他的生日午宴
He, like, let me come to his birthday lunch.
还给我提供工作
And he offered me a job.
对吗
Right?
他不该遭受这种苦难
He doesn't deserve this.
那个... 如果有任何我能帮忙的
And... so, if there's anything that I can do,
不要客气
let me know.
确实有点事需要你做
Actually, there is something.
-没问题  -你能去公寓
- OK. - Can you go to the apartment
拿他的床上用品和拖鞋吗
and get his bed things and slippers?
有深色方格的那双
The ones with the dark checks.
你不介意吧
You don't mind?
当然不 我...
No, no. I'd be...
我愿意尽绵薄之力
respectfully, uh, somberly willing.
谢谢
Thank you.
-现在就去吗  -麻烦了
- Now? - Please.
好 没问题
OK. All right.
玛西娅
Marcia, we can get
我们可以派科林或司机去取这些东西的
Colin or the driver to go and get his things.
我讨厌这只苍蝇在我面前叫唤
I don't need this fly buzzing in my face.
拖鞋 拖鞋 拖鞋 拖鞋
Slippers, slippers, slippers, slippers, slippers.
记住 千万别搞砸
Yeah, don't fuck it up.
腿真他妈长 格雷格 我有事找你
Fuckin' long legs. Greg! Hey, I need a favor from you.
怎么了
What's up?
父亲有些文件想让我们签署
Dad had some papers he wanted us to sign,
文件放在信封里
and they're in some envelopes,
信封在家 顺便带过来吧
just pick 'em up at the house, and bring 'em.
好的 文件在哪
Yeah. Where are the papers?
就在房子的某个角落
They're in the house somewhere.
装在信封里... 反正就在房里
In envelopes-- They're just in the house!
-懂了吗  -明白 我想着...
- You got it? - OK. I was imagining...
你太他妈高了 我脖子都快废了
Oh, you're fucking tall. This is hurting my goddamn neck.
我得走了 记着找到那些文件
I have to go. OK? Just find the papers,
然后带过来
and bring 'em back.
文件... 就在...
Papers, and... and... they're gonna be just...
我简直受够这段对话了
I am so done with this conversation.
-带过来 行吗  -好的 没问题
- Just handle it, OK? - All right. Yeah.
这趟最好别搞砸
Better not fuck this one up.
我可不想刊登洛根·罗伊死讯的报纸
I don't want Logan Roy's newspapers
出现在我家垃圾桶里
goin' through my trash cans.
-天呐 我们杀死了...  -洛根
- Oh, my God! We've killed... - Logan.
我们是混蛋
We're bastards!
关了它
Turn that off.
罗曼 关掉
Roman, no. Turn it off.
-我们杀死了...  -洛根
- We've killed... - Logan.
我们是...
We're...
外面怎么说
What are they saying?
谣言罢了
Just rumors, you know.
他被送进医院
He was taken to the hospital,
推特上有人说他死了
some of Twitter says he's dead,
还有很多人
and also a good deal of, um,
为他即将死亡而雀跃
of rejoicing at our father's potential demise.
能查出是哪些混蛋这么说
Can we find out who these fuckers are
然后... 揭发他们吗
and, like... report them?
或者直接怼回去吗
Or just, like, screen grab their shit.
-好的  -知道怎么做吧
- OK. - So we know? Yeah?
我不知道肯德尔在哪 但...
So, I don't know where Kendall is, but...
大家 我很遗憾
Hi. Really sorry, you guys.
谢谢 威拉
Thanks, Willa.
我们去那边坐吧
Why don't we sit over here.
肯在那
Oh, there's Ken.
真恶心
It's gross.
新闻出来了
News is out.
好吧...
OK, right. Well...
听着
So, um, listen.
我也不想这么做
I don't even want to think about this,
但我刚刚与提名委员会谈过了
but I just spoke to the nominating committee,
那个...
and, uh...
权宜之计是
the thing is that the plan
对外宣布我接替父亲
is to announce that I take over from Dad.
-不行  -你说啥
- Well, no. - Excuse me?
-你啥意思  -我的意思是
- What do you mean? - I mean,
我们还在等扫描的结果
we're waiting for the results of the scan.
你说的话毫无意义
It's a pointless conversation.
好 那我们谈谈
OK, well, let's talk about it.
我没法跟你谈谈 我伤心着呢
I can't talk about it. I'm upset.
我不伤心吗
Hey! I'm upset too.
至少你还穿着西装瞎指挥
Oh, not too upset to go and fucking plot
-没那么伤心  -去你的
- with the suits. - Fuck you! OK?
我都快因为耳充血听不到他们讲话了
I could hardly hear them for the blood rushing in my ears.
没有办法了吗 比如...
Isn't there a plan anyways? Like...
当然 有办法
Yes, there's a plan.
我他妈正跟你说呢
That's what I'm fucking telling you.
我和弗兰克将接手...
The plan is that Frank and I will take over...
-弗兰克被炒了 所以...  -没错
- Frank was fired. So.. - Yeah.
好吧 我们可以讨论一下
OK. Well, I mean, let's d-discuss
审视一下我们目前的境地 好吗
and just see where we are, right?
我不干
I'm not doing this.
如果爸撑不过去
If Dad dies, I don't want
我不想在他走的时候说他的身后事
to be talking about this shit when he dies.
他不会走的
He won't die.
太好了 谢谢你
Yeah, this is great. Thank you.
你好 老兄
Hey, man.
抱歉 我...  我真的很抱歉
Sorry, I'm... I'm really sorry,
但我没钱付车费
but I don't have any money for the cab.
抱歉 先生 我认识你吗
I'm sorry, sir, do I know you?
是啊 我早些时候在这边
Yeah, I-I was here a little earlier.
我在里面被打来着
I got assaulted a little in there.
能麻烦你帮我付一下车费吗
So can you pay for the cab, please?
她应该打电话的
She was supposed to call,
但是可能事情太紧急了
but maybe she didn't because there's an emergency,
所以她没打
uh, happening.
先生 抱歉
Sir, I'm sorry,
我不认识你
I don't know who you are.
好吧 他不肯借我钱
OK, so he's not gonna lend me the money.
我不知道 那个...
So, I don't know, um...
你明白吧...  算是他欠你钱了
You know, he... Pretty much, he owes you your money.
他欠我...
He owes me the...?
你最好给我钱 哥们
You better give me the money, dude.
你俩自己解决这事吧
You guys need to work this out for yourselves,
因为根本上讲 你俩其中一人
because basically one of you guys
差90块 对吗
hasn't got $14, OK?
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
您好 罗伊太太
Hello, Mrs. Roy?
谢谢
Thank you.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
真太奇怪了
It's so weird.
我其实挺喜欢医院
I actually like hospitals.
很多人不喜欢 但至少病人有了保障
Lots of people don't. But they're safe.
说起来挺怪的
The weird thing for me
这几天
is that I was, well,
我一直想和洛根谈谈
I'd been intending to talk to Logan,
我想向小西... 求婚
you know, and make a... make a proposal,
很正式体面的求婚
a very decent proposal, to Shiv.
其实很早之前就想得到他的祝福
Actually been meaning to ask for his blessing for a while,
但现在... 明显很难操作
but, uh... now it's very difficult.
你说话之前
You need to find the right time
得挑下时机场合
for these conversations.
说得对
Right.
奇怪的是我现在想
The weird thing I'm thinkin' now is,
你觉得我现在请求他 他会高兴吗
do you think Logan would still like to be asked?
我知道他不能回答
You know? I mean, I know he can't reply,
但等他醒来后知道我问过了
but would he appreciate the gesture
会不会欣赏这举动
if he was told about it later?
甚至...
Or even in the case...
最糟的... 情况
in the case of the worst... case,
起码能在他死后 对他的尸体说一声
would it have been nice to have asked his body?
有关洛根身体状况的流言仍在继...
Rumors continue to circulate about the health of...
他们准备好了
Hey, hey. They're ready.
结果出来了
They have the results.
好 我操
OK. Fuck.
你没事吧
You OK?
当然 他会没事的
Yeah. Yeah. He'll be fine.
他可能正在病房里吃着全家桶
He's probably in there eating a fucking chicken bucket
对着人嚷嚷呢
and yelling at someone.
是出血性中风
He's had a hemorrhagic stroke,
右脑深处的出血
a bleed in the deep right hemisphere
给丘脑和脑干造成了压力
that put pressure on the thalamus and the brain stem,
所以导致了他的昏迷
and that's what caused a loss of consciousness.
所以呢 会做手术吗
So, what, do you operate?
这种深处出血情况不适合手术 尤其是老年人
We don't do that with deep bleeds, especially in older patients.
-他不老  -老弟 他才过了八十大寿
- He's not an older patient. - Dude, he just turned 80.
但身体上 他就像
But physically, he's, like,
只有70岁 还很健康
still in his 70s, and he's in great shape.
但事实是 这种情况下
The evidence is that operating
并不值得做手术
in situations like these isn't worthwhile.
那你们打算怎么做
So, then, what do you do?
你不能干看着
You can't do nothing.
我们会继续观察
We will carry out regular observations,
希望能尽快看到好转
and hopefully we'll see some improvement soon.
这还不够 对吗 朱迪斯医生 这...
That's not good enough. Right, Dr. Judith? That's...
这是间好医院
It's an excellent department.
谢谢你告诉我这个
Well, thank you for your input,
但我们仍要尝试其他选择 希望你能理解
but you'll understand if we check out our options.
我的助手联系了纽约大学医院的安·威依曼
My assistant's been in touch with Ann Wieman at NYU,
我们可能会把爸转到那
and we might move Dad there.
不 他留在这里
No. He stays here.
然后在这痊愈
He gets better here.
我们可以商量下
Well, we can discuss.
我们讨论后会告诉你
We'll discuss and get back to you.
不 没得商量
No. No discussion.
我是他最近的亲属 是他的代理人
I am his next of kin. I am his proxy.
我来决定 谢谢
I am in charge. Thank you.
好吧 那...
Good. Well...
我们会把洛根转到格林伯格的套房
we'll move Logan to a suite in Greenberg.
我来领路
I'll show you the way.
你们肯定还有很多问题
I'm sure you have some questions.
在路上可以为你们解答
Feel free to ask me on the way up.
-我很遗憾 肯  -谢谢你能来
- I'm sorry, Ken. - Thanks for coming over.
听我说
OK, so look.
我们不清楚现在情况如何
We don't know what's going on.
他可能好转 可能不会
He could be fine; he could not.
但不管怎样 明天他都不会醒
Either way, he's not gonna be back tomorrow,
所以 简单来说
so, long story short,
你能担任首席运营官 带领董事会...
will you carry on as COO, step up on the board...
-做代理董事长吗  -是的
- Become acting chairman. - Yes.
-不行  -啥
- No. - What?
他把我开了 肯
He fired me, Ken.
他... 我...
He... I...
听着 我都不确定他知道自己在说什么...
Look, I don't know if he even knew what he was saying...
他的头脑是否清楚
if his brain was working.
他清楚得很
His brain was working fine.
不管怎样 你被解雇的合法证据
Well, whatever else, there's no proof, legally,
-都不存在  -不是这个问题
- that yesterday even happened. - That's not the problem.
-那是什么问题  -我不想当董事主席
- So what's the problem? - I don't want to be chairman.
我只是个侍从廷臣 在大场面里充个数
I am just an attendant lord, here to swell a scene or two.
这他妈是什么意思
What the fuck does that mean?
真的 别生气
Come on, don't do that.
我们一起可以做很多大事
We could do great things together.
可能吧
Mm-hmm.
你到底想要什么 弗兰克
So what do you need, Frank?
兆亿美元无人盯防的比特币
A jazillion dollars in unmarked Bitcoin.
我没有价码 肯
I don't have a price, Ken.
-我不懂了 弗兰克  -下次再聊
- Frank, I don't understand. - Ju... We'll talk.
肯德尔 你还有很多麻烦事等着处理
There's a lot of mess to be cleaned up, Kendall,
孩子 你能做到的
but you can do it, son.
你可以的
You can.
我说什么都不能让你改变主意吗
And there's nothing I can say to change your mind?
你父亲的事情我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your father.
肯尼 祝你好运
And good luck, Kenny.
好吗
Yeah?
我让格雷格把信托变更合同带来
I told Greg to bring the change of trust.
-什么  -他来了之后
- What? - And when he does,
我觉得我们应该签名
I think we should sign it.
没有律师在场 我什么都不会签的
I... I'm not doing anything without my lawyer present.
好吧 我会签的 我也会让康纳签的
OK. Well, I'm going to sign it, I'm getting Connor to sign it.
如果你不签 想想你会显得多他妈无情
It's gonna make you look pretty fucking heartless when you don't.
别做那傻逼表情吓我
Don't give me a fuckin' scary look.
你要是打我 我就玩死你
You hit me, I will fuck you up.
操
Fuck.
怕就好
Yeah.
你他妈怎么这么烦
God, you're so annoying.
闭嘴
Shut up.
-喂  -格雷格
- Hello? - Greg.
你找到罗曼要的合同了吗
Hey. Did you find those contracts Roman asked for?
我... 我找到了
Uh, I... Yes, I got 'em.
我觉得你应该拿错了
Oh, I think you have the wrong ones.
好吧
Uh, OK.
Right.
我该做什么
What, uh, what shall I do?
听着 现在情况很混乱
Look, there's a lot of confusion.
如果你不确定 或者找不到它
'Cause if you have any doubt, maybe you can't find them,
可能是最简单的情况了
and that might be simplest.
但如果我找到了
But if I do,
因为我...
'cause I...
我觉得我找到了对的合同
I think I have the right ones here.
别带来
Don't bring them in.
他改变主意了吗
Did he change his mind?
没有 我只是告诉你
No. I'm just telling you:
别把合同带来
Don't bring them in.
好吧...
Ok. Ok. S...
好吧 我懂... 懂了
All right, I get... I get it.
所以 到底怎么...
So, who's the...
我到底该听谁的
Like, what's the chain of command here?
你是更年长的吗
Are you the more senior sibling?
格雷格
Greg,
很简单
it's simple.
我在求你帮我个忙
This is a favor I'd like you to do for me,
我希望你能保密
and I'd like you to be discreet.
你找了会儿 但没找到
You stay for a while, you can't find them,
你就空手回来 好吗
you come back. OK?
-好  -谢谢
- OK. - Thank you.
这样更好
This is better.
听着 我知道你们不想谈这个
look, so, I know you don't want to talk about this,
我只是通知你们 董事成员罗曼
I'm just informing you, Roman as a board member
持股人小西
and Shiv as a shareholder,
我会暂时代理执行总裁和董事主席
I'll be taking temporary charge as CEO and Chairman.
眼下弗兰克对这个职位不感兴趣
Frank is not interested in the position at present.
不好意思 我现在不想跟你谈这事儿
No. I'm sorry, but even if we were talking about this,
就算要谈 也用不着你来做主
which we are not, it wouldn't necessarily be you.
那请问该他妈谁做主呢
I'm sorry, then who the fuck would it be?
我不知道 随便谁
I don't know. Anyone.
比如我
It could be me.
你脑残了吗
Are you insane?
-爸之前让我当首席运营官  -不是这样的
- Dad made me COO. - I don't think so, dude.
爸那时候脑子不清楚
Dad wasn't thinking straight.
我看他挺清醒的
I think he was.
你 当首席运营官吗
You? The chief operating officer?
-没错  -如果这都不是证明他
- Yup. - I mean, if that wasn't a sign
神志不清的证据 还能是什么
he was loco in the coco, I don't know what is.
我不是这么看的
Well, I don't see it that way.
拜托 这就是个和事佬的差事 小罗
Come on. It was a negotiating position, Rome.
他在玩你呢
He was fuckin' playing you
为了让你签信托变更合同
to get you to sign the change of trust.
你都不知道首席运营官是做什么的吧
Do you even know what it fucking involves?
老头子都半路咽气了
I mean, he conked out mid-game.
你说我是白痴吗
Are you calling me a dipshit?
没有 我爱你 老弟 但你不是做正经事的人
No. I love you, man, but you're not a serious person.
去你妈的 他还没死 轮不到你他妈说话
All right, fuck you. He's alive, you're not the fuckin' boss.
行了 拜托 都少说两句
All right! Come on. Let's not throw shit around.
现在麻烦一堆 冷静点 不要贸然行事
We're in the middle, so let's just sit tight. No sudden moves.
我们必须有所行动 市场要知道
We need to move. The markets are gonna
谁在管理公司
want to know who's behind the wheel.
我们要抢占话语权
We need to control the narrative.
"抢占话语权" 你射的时候也这么说的吧
"Control the narrative." You probably yell that when you cum.
"抢占话语权 抢到它...
"Oh! Control the narrative! Oh! Control it...
抢占话语权..."
Control the narrative! Uhh..."
滚蛋 我们在医院里
Fuck you. We're in a hospital.
是个人都知道
Everyone knows.
我们必须说点什么
We have to say something.
其实没必要 因为没人知道情况有多严重
No. Actually, we don't. 'Cause no one knows how serious it is.
所以我们什么都不用说
So we don't have to say anything.
我们必须要说
Actually, we do. The SEC.
证监会明文规定了...
There are rules, there are laws...
天呐 法律 我们千万不能违法
Oh, no. The law? Well, we can't break the law.
卡洛丽娜
Hey, Karolina?
有没有总裁缺席
Has a CEO ever been out of action
但是不公开的案例
and people haven't been told?
我印象里没有 苹果以前有过 不过...
Um, not that I can think of. There was Apple, but that...
可要是我们... 打算先缓缓
Right, but if we... wanted to drag our feet on this,
等我们搞清状况...
until we figure the moves...
只要我们获悉消息
Well, once we do know,
股东就有责任告知人们...
there's a duty to shareholders to let people...
可我不... 我不清楚这里的情况
Yeah, but I don't... I don't know what we know.
万一是过敏反应呢
I mean, this could be an allergic reaction.
-万一是流感呢  -得了吧
- It could be the flu. - Oh, come on.
人家花都他妈送来了 纸包不住火
Look at the fuckin' orchids. This is out there.
就像有人在火奴鲁鲁机场绑架我们一样
It's like we're being held hostage in the Honolulu airport.
但我们要是想说什么 除了...
But if we wanted to say something, you know, other than...
这是撒谎 小西
It's called a lie, Shiv.
编造故事就是说谎
When you say the thing that's not, that's a lie.
我们必须准备发布声明
We'll need to make a holding statement.
当然了 我会考虑你们的想法
Of course, I'm open to your suggestions
试着去... 润色一下
on how to... finesse it.
太好了 我们做出决定后会立刻告诉你
Perfect. We'll make a decision and get back to you shortly.
韦斯达公司的总裁兼董事长洛根·罗伊...
Logan Roy, CEO and chairman of Waystar corporation...
你觉得我该怎么办
So, what do you think I do?
我不知道 她说了什么
Well, I don't know. What did she say?
罗曼让我把文件带过去
Roman said bring in the papers,
小西不让我带
Shiv said don't bring in the papers.
那你得掂量
Well, I guess you need to decide
他们两个谁更重要
which one of them is more important?
我感觉罗曼... 在公司更有话语权
I guess Roman's... in the company,
不过小西看上去更像老板
but Shiv seems like, I don't know, more bossy?
好吧 你要不就带一部分文件去
All right. Well, can you just take some of the papers?
我还搞不懂这些拖鞋
Plus, I don't know about these slippers.
看上去全是方格纹的
Like, they're all plaid.
"方格图案"是方格纹的意思吗
Does "Checked" mean plaid?
这有花格纹的 有苏格兰方格纹的...
'Cause then there's gingham, there's tartan...
简直他妈的是十字形雷区
It's like a crisscross fuckin' minefield.
别管拖鞋了 格雷格
Oh, fuck the slippers, Greg.
你要制定个计划
You have to strategize.
我这不正和老妈你商量吗
I'm trying to strategize, Mom, with you!
可你一点忙也没帮上
But you won't strategize.
怎么了 肯德尔
Hey. What's up, Kendall?
本想打给出资人结果错打给我了吗
You mix me up with your sponsor?
听着 我就是提醒你一下
Listen, I'm just calling to issue a reminder.
你的"把柄"在我手里 懂吗
Your pecker's in my pocket, OK,
没蛋的孬种
Dickless Dickleby?
按我说的做
You do what I say.
别人怎么说随他们 但是我们不能出面
Let others say what they want, but we stay dark.
明白了吗 不准报道昨天敲定的事
You get me? No reporting on what went down yesterday,
那场闹剧
the turmoil.
我做什么你管不着
Well, I can do whatever I want,
因为沃尔特和我的卫星网站
because Vaulter and our satellite sites
有自主编辑权...
have editorial independence...
你签的文件里写得明明白白
as set out in that piece of paper you signed.
你知道那份文件对我来说是什么吗
You know what that piece of paper is to me?
屁都不是 懂吗
Nothing. OK?
我会射在那份文件上然后寄给你当贺卡
I'd jerk off on that paper and send it to you as a greeting card.
敢走漏风声试试
Simon says, Mum's the word.
小瘪三
Motherfucker.
不好意思这么晚找你
Hey. Sorry to bother you so late.
我们有活儿要干
Hey, let's put something together
罗伊家族的滑稽秀开演了
about the Roy family shitshow.
我是不想淌这趟浑水 但是
So, and I don't want to get into this, but
要不我们干脆否决肯德尔当总裁得了
maybe we should just cut off the whole Kendall CEO thing
这样局面也不会太难看
so that it doesn't get painful.
我也不是想上马
Well, I mean, I'm not looking for it,
但既然已经是首席运营官了
but I guess I'm already COO,
再走一步也不难...
so one more step...
你不能当
It's not gonna be you.
-为什么  -拜托
- Because? - Come on.
-我不懂你什么意思  -你懂的
- I don't know what that means. - Yes, you do.
谁当都不重要
Well, it doesn't matter who does it.
反正是临时的 谁当都一样
It's just temporary, so anyone will do.
没错 谁都一样
Yeah, sure. Anyone.
-汤姆  -汤姆
- Tom. - Tom?
好吧
OK, fine.
卡尔
Karl.
鸟人一个 伊娃
Prick. Eva?
婊子
Cunt.
好吧 所以是谁
Okay. So?
必须是老爸信任的人
Someone Dad trusts.
可爸除了弗兰克谁都不相信
But Dad doesn't trust anyone, except Frank,
自己图开心又炒了弗兰克
and he fired Frank for shits and giggles.
格丽呢
Gerri?
我不喜欢她
I don't love Gerri.
但我也不讨厌她
But I don't hate Gerri.
那就她了
So, Gerri.
我跟她聊聊
I'll talk to her.
格丽
So, Gerri.
你好吗
How ya doin'?
我很好
Oh, I'm fine.
他们就是在这儿把贝尔德带走的 所以有点...
This is where they brought Baird, so it's a little...
贝尔德
Baird?
对 贝尔德是我丈夫
Yeah, Baird. My husband.
小西的教父
Shiv's godfather?
他是不是... 有乌龟
Oh, does he, um... with the tortoise?
-没错  -操 我就说嘛
-Yeah. - Fuck, yeah. Of course.
-他现在怎么样  -他去世了
- How is he? - He's dead.
我记得 记得... 你...
I know. I know. I remember... you...
那啥 格丽
So, uh, Gerri, uh,
我想跟你说声谢谢
just wanted to say thanks
带领我们走出这场风暴
for captaining us through this shitstorm.
你做得很不错
Um, you do a good job,
格丽 你...
Gerri, you, uh,
你是... 你是个十足的工作达人
you're, um, you're a real good job-doer.
我完全不会跟同事调情
I suck at the whole corporate flirt thing.
你知道的 我...
You know, I just...
我喜欢涂上润滑油就啪啪啪 懂吗
I like to lube up and fuck, you know?
-好吧  -好
- ok. - ok.
那... 对于我和小西来说
So, um... for me and Shiv,
提拔肯德尔这件事不得行
the whole Kendall thing doesn't work.
所以我们想... 让你当总顾问...
So we were thinkin'... general counsel...
你知道"尸体"都埋在哪
you know where the bodies are buried.
而且恐怕是你亲手埋的
You probably buried 'em yourself.
那...
So...
你将会得到家族的支持
you would have the family's support
来介入 然后接手
to step in and take the reins.
这真是太慷慨了
That's a very generous offer,
可我还是要拒绝
but I'm going to have to decline.
好吧 我能问问为什么吗
OK. Can, uh, can I ask why?
为什么我不想要这份能把你脑子炸开花的工作吗
Why I don't want the job that makes your brain explode?
好吧 可...
OK, but, um, uh...
格-格丽 抱歉
G-Gerri, excuse me,
可我... 我一直认为你...
but I... I've always thought of you...
是个冷冰冰的婊子杀手...
and I mean this in the best possible way...
我这话绝对是在夸你
as a stone-cold killer bitch.
谁说你不会调情的
Who says you don't know how to flirt?
沃尔特
浑沌企业的滑稽秀
好吧
Ok.
沃尔特
浑沌企业的滑稽秀
我能跟你单独谈谈吗 可以吗
Hey. Can I get a moment alone with you, do you think?
-我... -你看到这个没
- I... - Have you seen this?
对你父亲的事我很遗憾
I'm so sorry about your father.
谢谢 能回避一下吗
Thank you. Would you give us a minute?
当然
Yeah.
谢了 威拉
Thanks, Willa.
汤姆 你介意回避一下吗
Tom, would you mind?
别这样 我跟她可不一样
Oh, come on. I'm not the same as her.
肯
Ken.
沃尔特正在宣传公司如何陷入混乱的故事
Vaulter's running a story about how the company's in turmoil.
这不是咱们的公司吗
Don't we own him?
"浑沌企业的滑稽秀"
"Shit Show at the Fuck Factory"?
对 没把握 意见不合
Yeah. Uncertainty, discord.
那不是啥好故事
That is not a good story.
"家庭成员相互支持"
"Family gets behind other member of family,"
这才是好故事呢
that's a good story.
去他妈的
Oh, fuck them.
乔布斯快死的时候 苹果什么都没说
I mean, when Jobs was dying, Apple didn't say anything.
我们在医院里 小西 大家都知道
We're in a hospital, Shiv. Everyone knows.
我们不能就把他弄起来挥他的手
We can't just prop him up and wave his hand
然后说他挺好的就像
and say he's fine like they did
他们在政治局或"老板渡假去"[电影]里做的那样
in the Politburo or Weekend at fuckin' Bernie's.
听起来倒是不错
I like the sound of that, though.
听着
Look,
你不能用价值来衡量一个人的一生
you can't put a value on a human life,
除非在我们的情况下 你反而能
except in our case, you rather precisely can
因为到明天交易开盘的时候
because when trading opens tomorrow,
我们会跌到谷底
we're gonna drop like a stone.
唯一的问题是 底线是多少
The only question is, what's the bottom?
我觉得我是最好的选择
I think I'm the best option.
我就想说
I just want to say that, uh,
如果要我去... 去拿三明治或咖啡
if you need me to... go get sandwiches or coffee
或者从区域公园升职到管理北美 我都行
or step up from Regional Parks and run North America, I can,
而且我会做 这是开诚布公的提议...
and I will. And that's just an offer on the table...
-滚蛋 汤姆  -你滚蛋 肯德尔
- Fuck off, Tom. - Fuck you, Kendall.
-别跟汤姆这么说话  -没事的 没关系
- Don't talk to Tom like that. - It's OK. It's fine.
我马上就要被任命了
I was about to be announced.
我是说 我怎么能不是合理的选择呢
I mean, how can I not be the logical choice?
因为本来你就要被任命了
Because you were about to be announced,
肯 然后你却没有
Ken, and then you weren't.
我说 我们唯一确定的是
I mean, the only thing we know for certain,
今晚绝对确定的
like for absolute certain, tonight,
就是爸不想让你来管理公司
is that Dad didn't want you running the company.
如果有张写着地球上七十亿人的名单
So if there was a list of 7 billion people on this planet
而老爸会从中选出个老板
that Dad would choose to be boss,
你会是最后的选择
we know you would be last.
爸把你炒了 兄弟
Dad fired you, man.
不 他没开除我
No, he did not fire me.
他说就是要再等一会儿
He said it was just gonna take a little longer.
可他那么说是为了礼貌
But he said that to be nice.
我觉得他的意思是
What I think he meant to say was
他希望妈生的是个开罐器
that he wished that Mom gave birth to a can opener
因为那个至少能有点用
because at least then it would be useful.
傻逼
You're a dick.
-你这也太... -太过了吗
- That's... - Too far?
听着 董事会要给我这个机会
Look, the board are offering this to me.
我不是真的需要你们的支持
I don't actually need your backing.
你事实上真的 真的需要
You actually really, totally do.
我觉得你需要
I think you do.
没有支持的话 老爸这么对你后
Without it, after what Dad did to you,
我们或许可以让法院来决定任何任命
I mean, we could probably take any appointment to court.
天呐 小西 我们现在要上法院了吗
Jesus, Shiv, we're talking about court now?
去你妈的
Fuck you!
我原本都不想谈这个的 记得吗
I didn't even want to talk about this, remember?
你对我... 你对我有什么意见
What do you... What do you have against me?
-没有  -没有吗
- Nothing. - Nothing?
你真想让我说吗
Oh, you want me to actually say?
-没错 我想  -你缺少杀手的本能
- Yes, I do. - You lack killer instinct,
你乳臭未干 没有经验 智商不高
you're wet, you're green, you're intellectually insecure,
-扯淡  -你的意志不够强大
- Bullshit. - you're not emotionally strong enough,
-你还有成瘾问题  -够了
- you have addiction issues. - That's enough!
我不全是这么想的 只是尝试转述老爸的话
I don't think all that, I'm just trying to be Dad's voice.
厉害 真是个"超好的"印象
Bravo. It was an excellent impression.
我就想说我不会搅进来
I just want to say I'm not getting involved.
好
Good.
但小西是对的
But Shiv's right.
我没有说我会当一个更好的总裁
I'm not saying I would make a better CEO,
我没说
that's unsaid--
你说你没说的时候就是说了
It's not unsaid when you say it.
不是 我在说我没说
No, I'm saying I'm not saying it,
所以 实际上 我没说
so, in fact, it is unsaid.
兄弟 你怎么不去帮帮威拉做作业呢
Hey, pal, why don't you go help Willa with her homework?
扎心啊 混蛋
Ouch. Asshole.
听着 你怎么不来决定一切
Listen, why don't you decide everything.
我不在乎 我就看看
I don't care. I just observe.
白头盔: 叙利亚民防组织 无涉政治 什么人都救
我就是联合国白头盔 好吗
I'm a UN white helmet. All right?
大家
Guys--
还能有谁呢
who else are you gonna get?
我觉得小西不错
I think Shiv would be great.
我是这么想的
That's what I think.
谢了 亲爱的
Thanks, honey,
但是... 没戏
but... no way.
她不在公司工作
I mean, she doesn't work in the company
没有在公司工作的经验
and has no experience of the company
市场会要吓坏
and the markets would freak,
除此之外 我同意你的看法
but apart from that, I agree with you.
我们有选择的
I mean, we have options.
当然 你们都可以要点吗啡
Sure. You could all ask for morphine
这样就他妈能待在你那无痛幻想世界里
so you can stay in your painless fucking fantasy world
兰花在里面载歌载舞
where the orchids dance
公司的管理者是他妈一只魔力独角兽
and the company is run by a magical fucking unicorn!
去你妈的选择
Fuck your options.
喂 这是格雷格的手机 我是格雷格
Hello, this is Greg on Greg's phone.
-格雷格 你怎么样  -挺好的 我在
- Greg. How ya doin'? - Yeah, I'm just, um,
我没在磨蹭
not dawdling.
你还他妈在那公寓里呢
You're still at the fucking apartment?
这也太久了吧
You've been there forever.
就是...
Uh, just, um...
我知道你在拿睡衣啥的
I know you're picking up PJs and all that shit,
就再拿件毛衣吧 我爸的 行吗
just grab a sweater, maybe, also. My dad's, OK?
-好的 哪件毛衣啊  -随便
- OK. Which sweater? - It doesn't matter.
不要洗过的 最好是他穿过的
Not something washed. Something that he's worn, maybe.
-如果你找到的话  -好的
- If you find one. - OK, yeah.
如果是他穿过的话 如果他...
If he's worn it, if his...
我怎么知道他穿过没
How am I gonna know if it's worn?
你闻啊 不会吗
Just smell it. OK?
上帝啊 我就是想要个闻起来像他的东西 行吗
Jesus! I just want something that smells like him, OK?
我就这点要求 还听不懂吗
I just want that. Is that enough for you?
哥们 这真窝心
Dude, that's really nice.
如果是我昏迷的话 也会希望有人这么做的
I would want that if this was my situation, too.
那我就去帮你闻一闻...
So I'll sniff some stuff for you...
就... 什么都行 另外如果你告诉别人这事
Just... Whatever. And if you tell anyone about this,
我就... 把你屌割掉
I will... cut your dick off.
而且别忘了我让你带的文件
And don't forget those papers I told you to bring.
还有 谢谢
And, uh, thank you.
我他妈在说啥
Fuck off.
好吧
Yeah.
我... 抱歉 我没想敲钟召唤你
I... apologize if my bell summoned you.
现在...
It's, um...
-现在是凌晨四点  -对 我睡不着
- It's like 4:00 a.M. - Yeah, I couldn't sleep.
我把孩子们哄睡后 想了想我错过了这么多乐趣 所以...
Put the kids to bed and thought I was missing all the fun, so...
他们怎么样
How are they doing?
-你问孩子们  -对
- The kids? - Yeah.
他们挺好的
They're OK.
也许你明天可以带他们来
Maybe you could bring them by tomorrow.
他们就可以... 你懂的 就可以来... 来问候下
So they can say their... you know, say their... hellos.
-好啊  -好
- Yeah. - OK.
你怎么样
How are you feeling?
挺好 对
Good. Yeah.
是啊 我怎么样
Yeah. How am I feeling?
妈的 你换个问题
Fuck. Ask me another?
-老天 你今天真难熬  -没错
- Jesus, what a day for you. - Yeah.
提名委员会想让我接任
The nominating committee want me to be the big boss.
是吗
Really?
但是小西和罗曼不挺我
But Shiv and Roman won't back me
就因为老爸午餐那会的发言
because of what Dad said at lunch.
老天
Jesus.
-对  -你这些家人真是...
- Yeah. - Ah, your family is so...
太操蛋了
fucked.
我很抱歉 可这...
I'm sorry, but... Wow.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
肯 我...
Ken, I...
怎么说呢 这... 我不知道
What can I say? It's... I don't know.
肾上腺素吧
Adrenaline.
身体机能的问题
It's just my body.
你在这我很高兴
I'm glad you're here.
是 我看出来了
Yeah. I can tell.
-等下 等一下  -不 我没心情
- Hey. Look. Stop. Stop. - No. I'm not in the mood.
有件事我必须跟你说
There's something I have to say to you.
-什么  -西沃恩·罗伊...
- What? - Siobhan Roy...
老天爷啊
Oh, my God.
...你愿意嫁给我吗
... will you marry me?
这... 他妈搞什么 你认真的
What... the fuck? Seriously?
我爱你
I love you.
我想做点什么冲冲喜
And I wanted to do something to make all this better.
我想在你爸还在的时候求婚
And I thought while your dad's still with us,
难道这样不好吗
wouldn't that be a nice thing?
我们就办个简单的婚礼
We can get a quick wedding.
我爸现在病危你跟我求婚
What is it about my dad dying in a sterile environment
你觉得这特浪漫是吗
that screams big romantic gesture to you?
因为今天糟透了 我以为...
Well, it's a horrible day, I thought...
我以为这好事... 一桩
thought it would be a nice... thing.
汤姆 喜不是这么冲的
Tom, you can't balance it out like that.
就像我不会... 因为你的狗死了就给你口活一样
I'm not gonna... give you a blow job when your dog dies.
懂吗
Right?
懂 好吧
Yeah. OK.
没关系 我判断失误 我懂
It's fine. I misjudged it. I get it.
别 对不起 亲爱的 我很抱歉
No, I'm s-sorry. Honey, I'm sorry.
我... 这情况...
I'm... This is...
别把我们的求婚放到这个场合里
Let's just not have this as the moment.
等你挑个合适的时间再求
Why don't you do this again properly another time.
可不是 我说真的 现在时机不对
No! Exactly. This is not the moment.
就当没发生 取消 取消 取消
This didn't happen. Abort. Abort, abort,
好的 行
Good. OK.
不过你要知道
But so you know,
你求我就同意
yeah, whatever.
-真的 真的  -真的
- Yes? Yes? - Yeah.
你再求的话 我答应
When it happens, yes.
真的 太棒了
Yes? Yes!
-真的吗  -真的 我...
- Really? - Yeah. I...
真的
Yeah.
-现在就是一场滑稽秀  -哪呢
- It's such a shitshow. - What is?
我的家人
My family.
我们的家人
Our family.
-我们的家人  -对
- Our family. - Yeah.
我把拖鞋拿来了
So I got the slippers.
谢谢你
Thank you.
没事 我终于找到了
Yeah, I finally found 'em.
请把它们放到那边 好吗
Can you put them in there, please?
好的
Yeah.
你拿到拖鞋了
So, you got the slippers.
是的
Uh-huh.
我猜这下你就成了白马王子了
I guess that makes you Prince Charming.
我猜是的
I guess so.
你说你想上玛西娅
You saying you want to fuck Marcia?
什么 不 为什么你要这么说
What?! No. Wh-Why would you say that?
你刚说的
That's what you just said.
不 我没说
No. It isn't.
你说你是白马王子的
You said you were Prince Charming.
-不 是你说的  -我开玩笑的
- No, you just said that. - I'm kidding.
逗你呢
I'm kidding.
好吧
Ok.
你知不知道...
Do you know that, uh...
你知不知道他给了我份工作
Do you know that he gave me a job?
什么工作
What job?
-我不知道  -好吧
- I don't know. - OK.
-你知道我什么时候开始上班吗  -不 我当然不知道
- Do you know when I start? - No. Obviously I don't know.
-我怎么会知道  -我不知道
- Why would I know? - I don't know.
我以为你可能知道 因为大家谈话的时候可能会提
I thought you might know 'cause I thought everybody's talking
比如 可能提到我
and, like, might be talking about me?
是 大家无时无刻不谈论着你
No, everybody was talking about you this whole time.
大家谈的都是你 格雷格表弟
Everyone was only talking about you, Cousin Greg.
我懂了
I get it.
呵呵
Ha ha.
听着
Hey. Hey.
等你 搞清楚了
When you, uh, figure all this out,
来找我 好吗
come in and see me. OK?
之后 我会罩着你
And, uh, and I'll look after you.
好吗
All right?
我说真的 我会的
I'm serious. I will.
-当然  -谢谢你 老兄
- Sure. - Thanks, man.
没关系
That's OK.
好的 回头见
All right, later.
放轻松 格雷格
Take it easy, Greg.
来这聊两句
Yo, come here for a second.
好了 听着
So, listen.
我一直在考虑... 这是我的愿景
I've been thinking... This is my vision.
我俩联手 我和你
We got for it. Me and you.
总裁和首席运营官
CEO and COO.
我和小罗老弟
Me and my homey Romey.
我以为你觉得我是脑残
I thought I was a fuckhead.
是白痴 不过是你自己说的
Uh, dipshit, and you said that.
你说我不正经
You said I wasn't serious.
抱歉 今天很难熬
Sorry. It's been a long day.
是啊
Yeah.
但是 老弟 说真的
But dude, seriously.
我和你 兄弟
Me and you, bro.
我可以教你
Like, I could teach you.
而你也 也可以教我
And you could, you know, teach me.
那小西呢
And Shiv?
你知道小西什么德行
I mean, you know what Shiv's like.
反正她都是爸爸的宝贝女儿 是吧
Ultimately she's a daddy's girl. Right?
她想安安稳稳的
I mean, she wants to play it safe.
我们才是搞革命的狂热分子啊
We're the ones with the nuts to fuckin' revolutionize.
好吧 我不是不感兴趣
OK, I'm not uninterested.
那么好 我们他妈的就这么做
All right, then, let's fuckin' do it.
有这么件事 格丽拒绝了最高职位
Here's the thing. Gerri just turned down the top job.
那这有什么用意吗
So does that mean something?
你他妈玩我呢
Are you fuckin' with me?
没有
Nope.
谁问了格丽
Who asked Gerri?
有人提议的
It was broached.
-有人提议吗  -是的
- It was broached? - Yeah.
谁提的 你提的吗 是你 对不对
By who? Did you broach? You broached it, didn't you?
别安在我头上 成吗 大家都在提议各种事
Don't pin the broach on me, OK? Everyone was broaching.
我就是想确定下对彼此的信任
Just want to make sure we trust each other.
开诚布公 好吗
Everything up front, OK?
好吧
All right.
好的
Ok.
要握手确定一下还是怎么样
Shake on it or something?
正式的吗
Official?
好吧
Oh. OK.
你好
Hi.
搞什么啊
Oh, come on.
好了 别搞了
Hey. Hey, knock it off.
谢谢你 威拉
Thank you, Willa.
听着 我请罗曼做代理首席运营官...
So, listen, I've asked Roman to be acting COO...
-首席运营官  -...协助我做代理总裁
- Actual COO. - ...to my acting CEO.
-然后你说  -我说 何乐不为呢
- And you said? - I said why not?
-狡猾  -妹 别闹
- Snake. - Sis, please,
我努力把大家聚在一起 在中间调停
I'm trying to bring everyone together here. I'm mediating.
-不管 我不同意  -我也是
- Well, I'm saying no. - Me too.
你他妈不是白头盔吗
I thought you were a fucking white helmet.
有时候和平卫士
Sometimes a peacekeeper has
也需要杀掉边界上的狂暴分子 懂吗
to go shoot a maniac on the perimeter, OK?
什么鬼啊 你为什么反对我 却同意格丽任职
What the fuck? Why would you say no to this and yes to Gerri?
格丽已经在公司二十年了 爸信任她
Gerri has been with the company for 20 years. Dad trusts her.
她年长 有智慧 是很成熟的人...
She's older. She's wiser. She's a mature person...
就像我一样
such as myself.
但她不想做这个工作
Well, she doesn't want it.
好的 那么依我看来 我们应该另选他人
OK, so in my opinion, we should find someone else.
-暂时的  -好吧 例如谁
- Temporary. - OK, like who?
我不知道 某个中立的人吧
I don't know, someone neutral.
伊娃或者... 美国杀人魔 什么...
Eva or... American Psycho, what...
-卡尔  -卡尔 对
- Karl. - Karl. Yeah.
但如果不是暂时呢
And what if it isn't temporary,
如果他将暂时转变为永久呢
what if he uses his position to make it permanent?
因为他不会那么做的 他人很好 他会给大家带咖啡
Because he wouldn't do that. He's nice! He brought coffee.
他给大家带咖啡
Oh, he brought coffee.
那我们"肯定"要他掌管公司
Then we should definitely let him take control of the company.
兄弟 他没有要掌管公司啊
Dude, he's not gonna take control of the company.
听着 这是在赌博
Look, it's a gamble.
要么是我跟罗曼还有咱一家人
It's either me and Roman and us as a family,
要么就是伊娃跟卡尔
or it's Eva and Karl,
或是公司里某些摆臭脸穿西装的黑暗势力
or some fuckface suit from the Deep State of the company.
他们可能会把公司从我们手上夺走
They could take the company out of our hands,
我们再也不能靠近它了
and we'd never get near it again.
如果爸醒过来 很虚弱
If Dad wakes up, and he's frail,
抬眼看着这结局
and he's looking at the end game,
你想成为告诉他 他的家族企业
you want to be the one who tells him
不再是由家族掌控的企业的那个人吗
his family business isn't family-run anymore?
也许你可以脱了干系...
I mean, maybe you could get away with it...
-毕竟 你是他的最爱  -操你妈的
- you know, his favorite. - Oh, fuck you.
但也许你不会再是他的最爱
But maybe you wouldn't stay his favorite
如果你把公司拱手让人
if you gave away the firm.
听着 我们6点30前要做一个声明
Look, we need a statement by 6:30.
所以你们需要想想...
So you just have to think...
废话放一边...
like, bullshit aside...
你们认为谁 真的 会是父亲偏好的人选
who do you think, really, Dad would prefer?
还好吗 亲人们
What's up, fam?
对... 你拿到文件了吗
Oh. Yeah... did you get the papers?
-什么  -文...
- What? - The pap...
信封里的文件 我给你打了电话
The papers in the envelope? I called you?
兄弟... 我的天 我太抱歉了
Dude... Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
所以意思是 没拿吗
So no, basically?
我一直在想你父亲
I was thinking about your dad,
-我在那里...  -好了 别担心
- I was up there... - Hey, don't worry about it.
我的脑子当时一团乱
My head was just messed up.
好了 我们必须发表声明了 现在什么情况
OK. We're gonna have to announce. Where are we at?
父亲生病时
While Dad is ill,
家族建议肯德尔掌管公司
the family proposes that Kendall run the company
罗曼做首席运营官
with Roman as COO.
本人同意
I hereby concur.
好的...
OK. OK...
我会让委员会了解家族的立场
I will let the committee know the family's position,
等董事会批准后 我们就可以宣布了
and pending board approval, we can announce.
-恭喜 肯德尔  -谢谢 格丽
- Congratulations, Kendall. - Thanks, Gerri.
还有罗曼 恭喜你
And Roman, congratulations.
太令人兴奋了
This is all very exciting.
很艰难的决定
Difficult decision.
说明一下
For the record,
我个人认为这他妈就是场灾难
I personally believe this to be a total fucking disaster.
好 很好
OK, good.
肯德尔 听我说
Kendall, um, listen,
我们得谈谈
we need to talk.
我很抱歉 我需要...
I'm sorry, I just need to...
我需要和你私下谈谈
I just need a conversation with you in private.
这是做什么
What is this?
有一些事你必须知道
There's a few things you should know.
好吧 没办法委婉地告诉你
OK, there's no way to put this nicely,
所以请原谅我如此露骨
so forgive me for stating it baldly,
我们面临巨大的债务问题
but, there's a huge debt problem.
你说什... 不会的
What are you... No.
-会的 30亿  -不 没有这回事
- Yes. Three billion. - No, there's not.
滚蛋 我应该知道啊
Fuck off. I'd know.
没人知道
No one knows.
好吧 只有我和弗兰克
Well, me and Frank.
那么... 爸呢
What about... Dad?
对 还有你爸
Yeah, your dad.
是他欠的债
Hence the debt.
格丽 他妈的到底什么情况
Gerri, what the fuck is going on?
钱都哪去了
Where did the money go?
1985年
In 1985,
洛根急需现金扩建公园
Logan needed cash badly for the expansion into parks,
所以他通过家族控股公司借了一笔贷款
so he took out a loan through the family holding company.
他知道除了弗兰克外
He knew that besides Frank,
其他董事会成员都不清楚原委
none of the other boards members could see what was happening.
之后 他又把那笔贷款
And then he added that loan
加给已经负债累累的公司
to the company's already considerable debt.
婊子养的
Son of a bitch.
好吧
Ok.
好
我们可以协商
We can deal.
是的 但肯德尔 问题是
Yeah, but Kendall, the thing is,
这针对的是韦斯达的股票...
it's secured against Waystar's stock...
当股价跌到130美元一股时
and when the stock hits 130,
他们可以全额追回债务
they can pursue repayment in full.
也就是说 如果他们决定这么做 会把我们吃干抹净
Which, if they decided to do that, would eviscerate us.
是啊 但没有这么做的先例 他们绝不会这么做的
Yeah, but there's no precedent for that. They'll never do that.
他们会重新谈判
They'll renegotiate.
-那视情况而定  -什么情况
- Well, that depends. - On what?
好吧 银行知道他们投资的那个人
Well, you see, the banks know that the man they invested in
不能再发挥作用了 现在对他们而言
can no longer function, and as far as they're concerned,
你只是个发型挺好看的小屁孩
you're just some kid with nice hair.
回味这一刻被你搞得
You're making it quite fucking difficult
真他妈困难 格丽
to savor this moment, Gerri.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
别跳
Don't jump.
我们本来期待目前能看到反应
We had hoped to see a response by now,
但我们只知道他情况很稳定 所以...
but what we do know is that he's stable. So...
如果你们想睡会觉 现在是个好时候
if you want to grab some sleep, this is a good time.
晚安 爸
Night, Dad.
很快再见
See you soon.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠